准备好露营之旅了吗
Ready for your big camping trip?
你确定需要的东西都准备好了吗
You sure you got everything you need?
除了一样没了我就会真正迷失的...
Everything but the one thing I'd truly be lost without...
你的凯美瑞
Your Camry.
我的导航坏了
My GPS is broken.
我们可以交换车吗
Can we trade cars?
我最近离开了我的房地产公司
I recently left my real-estate partners
开始自主创业
to strike out on my own.
但在开始面对疯狂的房屋市场之前
But before facing the wilds of the housing market,
我要先在优胜美地国家公园
I'm gonna boost my confidence
露营六个晚上 然后在川汤小屋度过一晚
with six rugged nights of camping at Yosemite National Park
来提振我的信心
and one at the Kawayu Lodge.
当然了 我也担心
I'm concerned, of course,
重新适应现代文明会有困难
about readjusting to civilization,
所以预定了花园套房
so I've reserved the garden suite
以防我更习惯睡在户外
in case I'm more comfortable sleeping outside.
因为我能想象到自己
Only because I am picturing myself
与大队人马举着手电筒在森林里找人的画面
in a line of people sweeping the woods with flashlights,
你确定在树林里待一周没问题吗
are you sure a week in the woods is a good idea?
亲爱的 要说有问题 那大概是准备过头了
Sweetheart, if anything, I'm over prepared.
我准备了两周的食物
I have two weeks worth of food,
净水器
water purifiers...
信号枪
a flare gun.
别在屋里挥那玩意儿
Oh, don't wave that thing around in the house.
给我一点信任好不好
Give me a little bit of credit.
我又不会在屋里开信号枪
I'm not gonna shoot off a flare gun in the house.
莉莉 图书馆发短信说
Hey, Lily, the library is saying
《斑斑独角斑马》
that "Stripey the Zebracorn"
已经拖欠两个月没还了
is two months overdue?
这...这是什么情况
What -- what's that about?
图书馆新来了个管理员
We have a new librarian,
她有点...
and she's a little...
她经常喝醉乱发邮件
She's been drunk e-mailing a lot.
真可怜
Oh, that poor thing.
莉莉 去把那本书找来
Lily, go find that book.
罚款从你的零花钱里扣
And the fine's coming out of your allowance.
你这人是不是什么鬼话都信
You'll really believe anything, won't you?
我才不会
I will not.
是吗 好吧
Really? Okay...
还记得你让你奶奶
Um, hey, remember when you had your grandmother
给我们寄一个阿巴拉契亚魔法玩偶吗
ship us a certain Appalachian hex poppet
-因为你觉得我们的房子有邪灵 -是啊
- because you thought our house had evil spirits? - Okay, yeah.
不然你还能更好地解释
Do you have a better explanation
为什么我们的墙里回荡着
of why there were cries and giggles
-哭声和笑声吗 -可以
- echoing through our walls? - ?Yes.
我们的装修工在某个通风口发现了这个
Our contractor found this in one of the vents.
听听
Listen...
没错 我觉得这是那种
Yeah, I think it's one of those dolls
给那些极有可能怀孕的
they give high-school girls
高中女生准备的娃娃
who are high risk for getting pregnant?
我们家什么时候来过那种姑娘了
When would one of those girls have been in this house?
应该是我在当莉莉保姆
I think I was babysitting Lily,
然后我记得最后好像开了个派对
and I kinda remember it turning into a party situation.
当时似乎空调排风很大
You know, I sort of recall the air conditioning blasting
我不得不硬塞一些东西到通风口里堵住
and I had to shove something in the vent to block it,
其实我已经很靠谱了
which was pretty responsible,
毕竟当时我朋友艾丽西娅
considering my friend Alicia
带了她的真宝宝来呢
brought her actual baby there.
太多青少年走上歪路
So many teens going down the wrong path.
我每天都目睹
I see it every day.
你好像在转移话题
Uh, seems like you're trying to change the subject
不承认自己容易被骗哦
from you being gullible.
那是因为我更有爱心
Only because I have a more pressing concern.
今天我要第一次作为代理副校长
Today, I have to oversee my first detention
监督留校察看的坏学生
as acting vice principal,
我在...我绞尽脑汁在考虑
and I'm -- I've just been racking my brain
我该如何触动这些孩子
of how I'm gonna reach these kids.
这是留校察看
It's, uh, detention.
直接说"闭嘴做作业"怎么样
How about "Shut up and do your homework"?
她...她是被鬼附身吗
What's -- what's wrong with her?
需要把魔法玩偶拿来吗
Should I get the hex poppet?
我在哭而已
I'm just cry-talking.
-我给卡尔换衣服的时候 脖子扭了 -糟糕
- I threw my neck out changing Cal. - ?Oh, no.
现在我一动 整个人都得跟着动
Now whenever I move, all of me comes with it.
天啊 这样吧
Oh, gosh. Oh, you know what?
干脆让我们照顾一会儿卡尔
Why don't you let us take baby Cal,
你去让人按摩一下
and you go get yourself a rubdown.
你真是天使
You're an angel.
应该不会超过几小时
Shouldn't be but a few hours.
你不会比我想象的还要蠢吧
Hey, are you an even bigger rube than I thought?
她的脖子根本没事
There's nothing wrong with her neck.
-我的天啊 宝宝 -怎么了
- Oh my God, the baby! - ?What?!
不
No!
他 他冲我眨眼睛呢
He -- he winked at me.
你一定会喜欢的 乔
You're gonna love it, Joe.
我爸当年带我去看像这样的飞行表演
My dad took me to an air show like this
来庆祝我12岁的生日
for my 12th birthday.
我们看到了蓝天使 战斗机
We saw Blue Angels, fighter jets,
一架B-52轰炸机
a B-52 bomber.
-什么被炸了吗 -我爸被灌炸了
- Something got bombed? - Well, my dad.
他跟几个飞行员比赛喝酒被灌倒
He got in a drinking contest with some fly boys.
结果也因此变得更好玩了
But that just made it extra fun,
因为最后成了我开车带我爸回家
'cause I got to drive us home.
乔 为什么堡垒
Joe, why is the fort
还在客厅中央
still in the middle of the living room?
-我需要 -需要干嘛 防印第安人吗
- I need it. For what? Apaches?
你被攻击了吗
Are you being attacked?
感觉现在就在被攻击
Feels like it.
快拆掉
Take it down.
我已经跟你说三次了
I've told you three times already.
你现在不拆的话
If you don't do it now,
我们就不去看飞行表演了
we're not going to the air show.
等等 不公平 为什么要惩罚我
Wait, no fair! Why am I being punished?
我没想到你们这会儿会在家
Oh, I didn't expect you guys to be home.
我们就打算来用一下泳池
Uh, we're just gonna use the pool.
杰 歌洛莉亚
Jay, Gloria...
歌洛莉亚
Gloria?
这是凯伦·菲斯科博士
This is Dr. Karen Fisk.
她是我们学校的律动教师
She's a movement teacher at my school.
你儿子非常有天赋
Your son is very talented.
非常高兴
Well, it's always very nice
能见到曼尼的老师
to meet one of Manny's teachers.
我去给各位倒点喝的
Why don't I get us something to drink
再准备些好吃的布朗尼
and maybe some delicious brownies
我本来打算扔掉的
that I was about to throw away
因为那是只给好孩子准备的
because they're only for the good children!
布朗尼你留着吧
Keep your brownies!
曼尼努力装成熟
It's cute, that grown-up routine
来博取他女朋友好感的样子太可爱了
Manny's putting on to impress his girlfriend.
她才不是他女朋友
She's not his girlfriend.
她是他的老师
She's his teacher.
歌洛莉亚 他是在
Gloria, he brought her home
以为家里没人的时间把她带回家
when he thought no one would be around.
曼尼从小时候起
Manny has been bringing his teachers home
就常带老师回家
since he was a little kid.
他的九岁生日派对最后变成了家长会
His 9th birthday party turned into a PTA meeting.
歌洛莉亚 我认为你这是
Gloria, I think you're just not seeing
故意无视你不想看到的
what you don't want to see.
相信我 杰 什么都逃不出我的眼睛
Believe me, Jay, I see everything.
牙医说新牙齿维持器应该明天就到了
The dentist says your new mouth guard should be there tomorrow.
艾丽克斯 你一晚不戴不会死的
Alex, I am sure you can make it through one night...
我哪知道
I-I don't know,
去材料实验室自己鼓捣一个来顶一下吧
hit the materials lab and whip up some mouth flubber.
克莱尔 谢天谢地
Claire, thank goodness.
运货卡车有点搞混了
There was a bit of a trucking mix-up.
尔文被安排去朱利安 不能去维塞利亚了
Irving was sent to Julian and can't get to Visalia.
那让达斯汀去维塞利亚
Well, send Dustin to Visalia
再让尔文去朱利安和拉蒙纳
and have Irving hit Julian and Ramona.
达斯汀不能同时送去维塞利亚和尔湾
Dustin can't hit Visalia and also Irvine.
那朱利娅能送去尔湾吗
Well, can Julia hit Irvine?
-不能同时去尔湾和塔斯廷 -那好
- Not Irvine and Tustin. - Fine...
让朱利娅去朱利安 拉蒙去拉蒙纳
Send Julia to Julian, Ramon to Ramona,
达斯汀去塔斯廷 尔文去尔湾
Dustin to Tustin, Irving to Irvine,
再由我亲自把破货车开去维塞利亚
and I'll drive the damn truck to Visalia!
-你吗 -是的 当然是我 玛格丽特
- You? - ?Yes, of course me, Margaret!
因为好像什么问题都得我来解决
'Cause I have to handle everything anyhow!
舍我其谁
If not me, who?
不 "琪谁"要去卡尔斯巴德
Oh, no. Mi Hu is going to Carlsbad.
这些就是你们的未来
These are your future,
而它们飞出了窗户
And they're headed...out...the window...
一去不复返
never to return.
是你掉的吗 教练
You drop this, Coach?
是的
Yes.
肯定是万圣节到了
Oh, it must be Halloween,
因为有人在交头接耳[发巧克力棒]
because somebody's passing out snickers!
肖恩
Shane?
抱歉 我无意打断你
Sorry, I didn't mean to interrupt.
没关系 肖恩
Oh, it's okay, Shane.
我了解你这一型
I know your type.
硬汉 自以为聪明
Tough guy. Know it all.
这就像照镜子一样
It's like looking in a mirror.
没错 肖恩
That's right, Shane.
我当年和你一样
I was you.
直到当地的警长把我抓进了牢房
Till a local sheriff put me in jail.
那是个名叫"吓到你乖[变直]"的项目
In a little program called Scared Straight,
现在我大声说出来
which, now that I'm saying it out loud,
才觉得似乎还有另一层意思
could have had a double meaning.
我在拘留所关了24小时
24 hours in the joint
和地狱里来的危险角色关在一起
with some of the most dangerous characters this side of Hell.
或许
Maybe,
或许你们也想见见他们
Maybe you'd like to meet some of them.
我不知道你这是在瞅啥
I don't know what you're lookin' at,
因为爷不记得批准你瞅我了
'cause I don't ever remember sellin' you a lookin' license!
看来现在是凌晨五点的麦当劳门口
Hey, it must be 5:00 a.m. outside the McDonald's,
因为又有小鲜肉到货了
because the fresh meat just got delivered!
鼬爷我贼喜欢小鲜肉
And the Weasel likes fresh meat!
你别碰他
Hey, you back off him!
那是我的新宠
That new boy's mine!
小卡舅夫啊
Uncle Cam...
点赞
"Like."
我朋友 比利
My friend, Billy.
比利·克拉布
Billy Club.
-小卡啊 -看我捶你
- Ay, Cam... - Whack!
点赞
"Like."
你知道怎么开卡车吗
Do you even know how to drive a truck?
不 玛格丽特 我不知道
No, Margaret, I don't...
但和世界上其他人不同
but unlike the rest of the world,
有时我会靠自己解决问题
sometimes I just figure things out on my own.
倒车
Backing up...
闭嘴 玛格丽特
Shut up, Margaret.
生存影像日志 第一条
Survival vlog, entry one.
在徒步八公里又乘着急流而下后
After a five-mile hike and ride down some rapids,
我决定在这里扎营
I've decided to make my camp here.
急流非常危险
The rapids were treacherous.
顺流而下后
I took on water
我很快意识到我唯一生存下去的办法
and quickly realized my only chance for survival
就是将我的同伴推下水
was to push my companion overboard --
我如影随形的同伴 恐惧
my constant companion...fear.
求你们别开到我的盲区
Please stay out of my blind spot.
并道
Merging.
Merging!
抱歉
Sorry!
这就是事实
Here's the thing.
在野外 你要么在挑战前畏缩
In the wild, you either shrink from the challenge,
要么意识到有信心就成功了一半
or you realize that confidence is half the battle
变成环境的掌控者
and you become the master of your environment.
好吧
Okay...
好的
All right.
谢谢 谢谢 谢谢你
Thank you, thank you. Thank you.
也不是很难
This isn't so bad.
挺好的
Yeah.
没错 普锐斯 给姐让路
That's right, Prius... Move it.
没错
Yep.
有时你只需要挺起胸膛
Sometimes it's just a matter of thrusting your chest out,
捍卫你的立场
staking your claim...
让大自然知道 现在由你这新警长做主
and letting nature know there's a new sheriff in town.
西班牙辣香肠和大蕉都太好吃了
This chorizo, these plantains, it's all so delicious.
你什么时候开始爱吃哥伦比亚菜了
When did you develop a taste for Colombian?
这叫帕伊萨拼盘
It's called bandeja paisa.
天资好 人聪明
Oh, talented, smart,
还会说西班牙语
and speaks Spanish.
拜托
Oh, please.
谁不想摸他脸颊啊
Everybody wants to touch those cheeks.
他看起来像教堂天花板上
He looks like one of those babies
吹出云彩的肥宝宝
that blow a cloud across the ceiling of a church.
凯伦教授 告诉我们你教什么课程
So, tell us, Dr. Karen, what do you teach?
直接展示给你们看最好不过了
Well, the best way would be to show you.
-不如我们动起来 -真有趣
- Why don't we find our legs? - ?Fun.
站在我旁边跟着我做
Now stand beside me and follow along.
想象你正提着两桶水
Imagine you're carrying two pails of water.
深呼吸
Deep breath.
不不不 你不该挺胸
No, no, no. Your chest shouldn't be lifting.
来把你的手放到我脖子上
Come place your hands on my neck.
感觉到我的呼吸有多顺畅了吗
Do you feel how still and open my breathing is?
我这里有些敏感
Oh, a little sensitive there.
是啊 这里有块小吻痕
Yeah, you have a little bite there.
怪我下嘴没轻重
Oh, my bad.
你有点太用力了
Okay, that's a little tight.
但我现在知道曼尼柔软的手是随谁了
But I can see where Manny gets his soft hands from!
-真是大开眼界 -妈 妈
- Oh, that's very, very eye-opening. - Mom. Mom.
我们去厨房看看甜点好了没
Uh, let's check on the dessert in the kitchen.
什么样的学校会允许教师和学生约会
What kind of schools allow a teacher to date a student?
我想艺术学院都这样
I'm guessing any art school.
他不能和三十岁的人约会
He can't date a 30-year-old.
曼尼还是个孩子
Manny's still a child.
我初次见到曼尼时他就不是孩子了
Manny wasn't a child when I met him.
曾经有十年时间
Look, there was a 10-year period
每年感恩节
where there was at least one empty chair
都至少有一个孩子不来看我
at my house every Thanksgiving
因为我总是喋喋不休
because I had a lot to say
挑米奇尔和克莱尔对象的刺
about who Mitchell and Claire were dating.
我做父亲就这一个败笔 吸取我的教训
So learn from my one and only parental mistake.
或许凯伦和我该走了
Uh, maybe Karen and I should head out.
-我觉得局面有些尴尬 -不不不
- I'm sensing some tension. - No, no, no.
这是你家
This is your house,
你在家里不该感到不舒服
and you're supposed to be comfortable here.
留下吧
So, just hang out.
再喝些葡萄酒
Have more wine.
别担心开车的事
And don't worry about driving.
你们今晚可以留下过夜
You can spend the night here tonight.
你确定吗 妈
Are you sure, Mom?
确定 我去再拿些葡萄酒来
Yeah, I'm sure. I'll go get some more wine.
对她走路的姿势有什么建议吗
Any tips on how she moves?
我从没见过这样的身姿
I've never seen anything like it.
是吧
Right?
你好啊 肖恩
Hello, Shane.
代理副校长塔克
Acting Vice Principal Tucker.
我知道你认为你现在很讨人喜欢
I know you think you're pretty cute right now,
但在太阳落山前
but before this day is done,
我会让你承认是你上传了那个视频
I will get you to admit you sent out that video.
的确是我上传了那个视频
I did send out that video.
我就知道你会老实招来
I knew you'd crack.
听着
Look, uh...
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我只是很需要让这些孩子接受我
I just really need these kids to accept me.
不 肖恩 你不需要
No, Shane, you don't.
不过是他们很受欢迎
Because they're popular,
让你认为你需要他们的认可
you think you need their approval.
我是个警察
I'm a cop.
是吗
Oh, are you, now?
我们很关注这所学校内的毒品买卖情况
There's concern about some drug traffic at this school.
我是来卧底将他们一网打尽的
I am here, undercover, to shut it down.
是吗是吗
Okay, yeah.
我其实早就知道你是警察
Okay, well, I kind of always knew you were police.
当然
Well, sure.
你也是执法人员
You're law enforcement, too.
同类之间有感应
We know our own.
警察的双眼
Cop eyes.
好
Okay.
具体是怎么个情况
So what's the play?
有种新型化合致幻药叫迪克吗啡
There's this new designer drug called Dexomorphone.
孩子们叫它"傻子"
?Kids are calling them "Dum-Dums."
今晚北校区举办篮球赛时
So there's this big deal going down tonight
会有一场大买卖
on the north campus during the basketball game.
你想让我帮忙逮捕罪犯
And you want my help with the bust.
是的
Yes.
你的任务就是不要接近那里
By being nowhere near there.
我不想吓跑这些毒贩子
I don't want to spook these dealers.
收到
Copy that.
但以防你需要后援
But in case you need backup,
我应该在北校区附近待命
I should be near north campus.
或者绝对不要接近
Or nowhere near there.
或者去
Or there...
但缩在我车里以防被人看见
but slouched down in my car so no one sees me.
或者留在你家里
Or at your house.
了解
Right.
好的
Okay.
警察的双眼
Cop eyes.
好了 好了
Okay. Okay.
我们要去外面散步吗
Are we gonna go outside?
是的 去散步
Yes, we are.
小心
Careful.
我告诉过你多少次不要把这个扔在这
How many times have I told you not to leave this here?
会有人被绊倒的
Someone's gonna trip on it.
我现在有很多烦恼顾不过来
There's a lot going on with me right now.
我的身体开始发育了
My body's changing.
行了 你总用这个借口
Okay. You always use that.
今天你要学会负责任
Hey, today, you're gonna learn about responsibility.
今天 你得照顾一个小宝宝
Today, you are gonna take care of a baby.
你想要玩具吗
Do you want a toy?
给你点严厉的爱
Little tough love.
要我说早该这样了
Long overdo, if you ask me.
但这样对你有好处 亲爱的
But it's gonna be good for you, sweetie.
他哭了
He's crying.
宝宝都这样
Well, that's what babies do.
你得抱起来哄哄他
You just got to pick it up, and you got to soothe it.
那好吧
All right, then.
-好 -没事的
- Okay. - It's okay.
-起作用了 -很好
- It worked. - ?Good.
到晚上前都要保持住
Just keep it up for the rest of the afternoon.
等等 我不知道该怎么做
Wait! I don't know what I'm supposed to do!
欢迎体验家长生活
Well, welcome to being a parent.
生存影像日志第二条
Survival vlog number two.
我潜水里去 试图找回我的装备
I descended into the water attempting to retrieve my gear.
踩到了很滑的石头
I encountered slippery rocks...
跌进了又冷又急的水流
...a cold, brisk current,
尽管我没有影像证明
and although I have no photographic evidence of it,
我看到了大海蛇
a sea serpent.
紧接着我翻腾时拍晕了一只路过的鳟鱼
My ensuing thrashing stunned a passing trout.
然后我找到了一些野莓和蜂蜜
I then foraged some wild blueberries and honey
蜂蜜是从那个我后来才发现
from what turned out to be a not --
原来还没完全被废弃的蜂巢里弄的
altogether abandoned hive.
这都证明了
Just goes to show you...
我不需要什么高级的设备
I don't need all that fancy equipment.
菲尔·邓菲可以在野外生存 就连...
Phil Dunphy can survive in the wild, even --
听起来挺大只的是吧
That sounded big, didn't it?
幸好我闻起来像野莓 蜂蜜和生鱼
Good thing I smell like berries, honey, and raw fish,
我简直就是人形的
so I'm basically all three courses
野熊最爱三道菜
of a bear's favorite meal!
就是这样
That's right.
都听听老娘的汽笛吧
Watch them scatter.
-你好 -你好啊 亲爱的
- Hello? - Oh, hi, honey!
今天大多数时间我手机都没信号
I've been out of cell range for most of the day.
我就来关心一下看你好不好
I just wanted to check in, see how you're doing.
很好啊 太好了
Oh. Great, great.
这空气 这树木...
The air, the, uh -- the trees...
苔藓通常都是长在树干的北面对吧
Moss only grows on the north side of trees, right?
我感觉我有可能在绕圈子
I feel like I might be walking in circles.
有没有什么傻子指路苔之类的啊
Is there something called, uh, fool's moss?
不知道耶
I don't know.
你有点上气不接下气 还好吧
You sound out of breath. Is everything okay?
不好啊 克莱尔 我在害怕有熊
No, Claire, I'm worried that a bear
甚至是一家子的熊在追我呢
or even a family of bears is hunting me.
我当然没事啦
Of course I'm okay.
我才刚到几个小时而已
I've only been out here for a couple hours.
你觉得我是什么软脚虾吗
Uh, uh, what kind of man do you think I am?
感觉我们两个都在进行各自的冒险
Well, it sounds like we're both having an adventure.
我刚过地磅 你猜我多重
I just got on a scale, and guess how much I weigh.
五吨呢
5 tons!
是啦 我们之前过节都胖了几斤
Yeah, well, we all put on a few around the holidays.
我晚点再打给你吧
Mwah! Let me call you back a little later.
挂之前 我先发给你一张
Meanwhile, uh, I am sending you a pic
我在最后已知出现位置享受自然的照片
of me enjoying nature at my last known location
穿的是我十分容易辨识的防水夹克
in my very identifiable red Gore-Tex jacket.
最后记得 付家里的园丁工资
Anyhoo, leave a check out for the gardener,
还有 是你让我人生有意义
and you gave my life meaning.
你很爱笑 是不是啊
You're a giggly one, aren't ya?
真怀念这声音
Oh, I miss that sound.
您好 我能看看嘛
Hi. Can I look?
莉莉 怎么样了
Hey, Lily, how's it going?
我很努力了
I'm trying my best,
但我还是不确定做得对不对
but I don't really know what I'm doing.
在它身上犯错总比以后对亲生的犯错好
Well, better to make your mistakes on this one.
懂吧 你等我一下
You know? ?Oh, hold on one second.
有人给我发你大爸的影片
Oh, someone's sending me a video of daddy.
别啊 别又是鼬哥 好了
No, not the Weasel. Okay.
-宝贝 我晚点再打给你好吗 -别挂
- Honey, I got to call you back, all right? - Wait!
天啊 他肯定受尽屈辱啊
God, he must be so humiliated.
你知道他是[像]个娃娃吧
You know he's a doll.
谢谢 谢谢 多谢夸奖
Thank you. Thank you. That's sweet.
谢谢
Thank you.
-米奇尔 -小卡
- Mitchell. - Cam. ?Hey, hey, hey!
我看到到处传的那个影片了
I saw that video that's going around.
-我替你感到难过 -我无所谓
- I am so sorry. - Oh, doesn't bother me.
那就好 很好 因为你不该难过
Good! Good, 'cause it shouldn't, you know?
你也是为了学生好
You're just trying to make a difference.
如果他们不懂你的苦心
If those kids don't appreciate that,
是他们自己的损失
that is their loss.
是啊 而且...
Yeah. And...
-这也是一个卧底大行动的一部分 -什么
- ...it's part of a big sting operation. ?- What?
其实我不应该告诉你这件事
So, I shouldn't be telling you this,
但是拍摄这影片的学生 肖恩
but Shane, the guy who shot the video,
其实是个卧底警察
is actually an undercover cop.
他拍这个影片的目的
Oh. ?Yeah, and he did the video
是有点故意要羞辱老师
to sort of, like, humiliate me
好在坏学生里混出名堂
to get some street cred.
而今晚有一场重大的毒品买卖
And there's a big drug deal going on tonight,
但他要求我不要插手
but he wants me to steer clear.
还有别人知道
Is anyone else aware of
肖恩电影般的双重身份吗
Shane's "21 Jump Street" double life?
他当然不会到处宣传
Well, he's not gonna broadcast it
让别人知道这事啦
out loud for everyone.
但他有给你看文件或是证件之类的吧
But you did get some paperwork or identification?
你别说了 你知道吗
Okay. You know what?
我觉得其实挺好笑的
I think it's hilarious that
你不相信的这个人是个英雄
the person you don't trust is a hero,
而他正在打击校园的迪克吗啡
who's helping fight the Dexomorphone problem
-这如瘟疫般... -等等 什么鬼
- that's plaguing... - I'm sorry. What?
那药品的街头名字叫"傻子"
The street name is "Dum-Dums,"
而肖恩说这傻子已经到处都是了
and Shane says there's literally Dum-Dums everywhere.
好的 所以肖恩
Okay. So, Shane --
不是个喜欢羞辱你的16岁毒品贩子
not a 16-year-old drug dealer who enjoys humiliating you --
而是个娃娃脸警察
but a baby-faced police officer,
他授权于你
has deputized you,
让你进行的第一个任务
and your first assignment
就是离他越远越好
is to stay as far away as possible
因为有个叫"傻子"的毒品买卖要进行吗
from a huge "Dum-Dum" deal that's about to go down?
小卡 你不...
Cam, I mean, come --
我很爱你信任别人这点
I love how trusting you are,
但当你开始没意识到
but when you start missing things
这么明显的事情时... 你懂的
that are that obvious, then, well, you know,
我不用再说下去了
I don't have to say anything more.
我可以自己弄完
You know, I can finish up here
你想上楼就去吧
if you want to go upstairs.
不用不用 没事
Nah, nah, I'm fine.
其实呢
You know, um...
妈还挺让我讶异的
Mom really surprised me before.
因为这是她第一次把我当成大人般对待
This is the first time she's treating me like an adult.
凯伦很好
And Karen's great.
跟一个成熟的女性在一起很好
I mean, It's nice to be with a mature woman,
她们比较有经验
someone with experience.
你们俩还没睡过吧
So you two haven't slept together, huh?
她提议我们来家里"睡"
She suggested we come here.
我说行吧
I said fine.
但你不知道我看到你们在家时有多庆幸
You don't know how relieved I was you guys were home.
但结果妈这么坦然接受
But then Mom was so cool with it.
那个哥伦比亚疯婆子上哪去了呢
I mean, where's the crazy Colombian
我唯一一次需要她救 她不见了
the one time I need her?
已经擦干了
This is dry.
但你是喜欢凯伦的吧
But you like Karen, right?
很喜欢啊 可是...
A lot, but, I mean...
她比我大不少已经有点糟糕了
bad enough she's older than I am,
她还是我的律动教授
she's also a movement professor.
我的老天爷 我过去人生中
I swear to God, before today,
从来没听过律动与教授这两词合在一起
I'd never heard those two words together.
但现在却不停听到
Now it's all I hear.
听我说
Look...
紧张是很正常的
it's normal to be nervous.
别做任何你还没准备好的事
Don't do anything you're not ready for.
跟她谈谈你的感受
Talk to her about what you're feeling.
你会很惊讶 一场开诚布公的交流
You'll be surprised how much easier things get
能让事情变得简单多少
after one honest conversation.
谢了 杰
Thanks, Jay.
一个好了 还有一个
One down, one to go.
乔 要来谈谈了吗
Joe?! You ready to talk?
就为了点燕麦葡萄干饼干吗
For oatmeal raisin?
别浪费我的时间了
Don't waste my time.
这货正点吗
Is this stuff any good?
必需得正点啊
It better be.
我花掉一半的成年礼基金买的呢
I laid out half my bar mitzvah bonds to get it.
对了 塔克教练的影片很赞啊
Sick movie of Coach Tucker, by the way.
你们喜欢那影片就好
Glad you enjoyed the film, boys.
现在你们也能当影片主角了
Now you can be in one of your own!
你他妈在干嘛呢
What the hell are you doing?!
干我的工作
My job.
看来我是个真真正正的副校长啊
I guess I really am a vice principal.
一个《迈阿密重案组[副]》校长
A Miami vice principal --
不对 好像不需要那个"迈阿密"也行
No, I guess it doesn't really need the "Miami," does it.
我真是信了你的邪
I can't believe this.
被我人赃并获了吧
You're busted.
我们来看看你身上有什么
What do we got here?
我猜猜 有你的毒品钱...
Oh, let me guess -- your -- your drug money,
对讲机
walkie-talkie.
这是什么
What's this?
警徽
A badge.
米奇尔真是欠你个天大的道歉啊
Mitchell's really gonna owe you an apology.
坚持开车 兄弟
Drive strong, brother.
克莱尔
Hey, Claire.
亲爱的 你怎么样啦
Hi, honey. How's it going?
坐在一条完美的山林小溪旁
Just sitting here by a perfect mountain stream.
没有什么比大自然中的原始之美还赞的了
Nothing beats the raw beauty of the great outdoors.
你那边怎么样了
How's everything going there?
好得不能再好
Couldn't be better.
我现在在回家的路上
I'm on my way home now,
我们今天缺了一个卡车司机
but we were down a driver,
所以我得到开卡车的机会
so I got to drive a truck today,
我真是爱死了
and I'm loving it.
让我感觉自己像个真正的爷们
Makes me feel like a real man.
是吗
Yeah?
那是什么感觉啊
What's that feel like?
你发生什么事了吗
Something going on with you?
亲爱的 其实我... 我没有跟你坦白
Honey, I haven't been, uh, totally honest with you.
不是我自己离开地产公司的
I didn't quit Woosnam, Keneally & Dunphy.
他们... 是他们让我走的
They -- They asked me to leave.
亲爱的 怎么回事
Oh, honey. What happened?
反正就是
Well, you know,
他们都是很野性很凶狠的一群人
those guys have always been super aggressive,
而他们觉得
and they didn't feel like
我没有他们那样的
I have the same killer instinct
杀手本性之类的
that -- that they do.
或许他们说的没错
Maybe they're right.
所以你这个神经病露营就是为了这个吗
Is that what this whole crazy camping thing is about?
证明自己是个硬汉
Proving how tough you are?
可能... 有一点吧
Maybe, a little,
尤其是我现在得自己出去闯
especially since I'll be going out on my own.
菲尔 你在独自承受的不是小事啊
Phil, this is a huge thing you've been going through.
你为什么没跟我说呢
Why didn't you say something?
你这周这么忙
Well, you've had such a busy week.
你到处救火 我不想自己也给你放火
I don't want to be another fire you had to put out.
你听我说
Okay, listen to me.
还记得我刚从爸那里接手公司时多害怕吗
Remember how terrified I was when I took over for my dad?
在我首日要当老板的前晚
The night before my first day in the big office,
我睡不着 心砰砰跳
I was up, heart pounding,
在客厅疯狂来回踱步
pacing a hole in the living-room floor.
突然你就来了
And suddenly, you were there.
你把手臂放我肩膀上
You just put your arms around me,
让我意识到
and it made me realize
一切风雨都有你来陪伴
I'm not going through this alone.
忘了你的白痴合伙人们
So forget your idiot partners
以及你想要在这次露营
and whatever it is you're trying to prove
证明的一切白痴事情
with this stupid camping trip.
你做事可厉害了 还有...
You're great at what you do, and also...
什么
What?
你怎... 怎么...
How -- How --
我要挂电话了
I'm gonna hang up now.
我爱你 再见
I love you. Goodbye.
你电话上听起来不太对劲
You didn't sound so good on the phone.
所以我就打给酒店
I called the hotel,
他们说你提前入住了
and they said you checked in early.
亲爱的 我知道我常抱怨
Honey, I know I like to complain
总有人来找我解决他们的问题
about people coming to me to solve their problems,
但永远不许你有问题不找我帮忙
but don't you dare not come to me with yours.
其实呢 如果你不想要别人
By the way, if you don't want people
总是来找你帮忙解决他们的问题
to come to you to solve their problems all the time,
那你就不要那么厉害啊
maybe don't be so good at it.
既然你这么喜欢野性...
Now that you're so into the wild...
我喜欢这话的走向
I like where this is going.
别这样 求你了
Don't...do that, please.
你还好吧
You okay?
乔在楼下的小堡垒里睡觉
Joe is sleeping in a fort downstairs,
而曼尼在楼上跟个博士睡
and Manny's upstairs sleeping with a doctor.
-我都搞不懂还有什么规矩了 -没人懂
- I don't know what the rules are anymore. - No one does,
但无论如何
but for what it's worth,
我觉得你做了正确的选择
I think you made the right call.
老娘起码得赢一场
I am at least winning one of these fights.
要去攻打堡垒了吗
Storming the fort?
我要下楼去把他给抓出来
I'm gonna go and drag him out of there
拖他回床上睡觉
and put him in his bed.
我好歹还比乔高大
I'm still bigger than Joe,
虽然曼尼也还是...
even though that Manny's, like...
相信我
Trust me.
曼尼心里的小男生一直都在
The little boy in Manny isn't gone yet.
终于啊 你去哪了
Finally, where have you been?
我带卡尔出去散步了
I have been out walking Cal.
你猜谁在我后面
And guess who's right behind me.
其实我才是...
Actually, I've been the one who...
配合得好就能去迪士尼乐园玩的女孩
Will be going to Disneyland if she plays her cards right.
我的小天使在哪里
Where's my little angel.
跟我说说你按摩怎么样了
Tell me about your rub down.
糟糕
Oh, oh boy.
没事 我能捡起来
Oh, I can get it.
我现在轻松又放松 捡东西什么的都没问题
Now I'm so free and loose, I can pick up anything, move around.
是的 我就像个猫头鹰
Yep, I'm like an owl.
我的小天使来啦
There is my little angel.
真是太谢谢你了
You know what? Thanks for this.
让我请你吃点东西 来吧
Let me treat you for a bite. Come on.
莉莉 我们马上回来
Lily, we'll be right back.
-他表现好吗 -超安静 超乖
- How was he? - So quiet, so easy!